Contact

lazelazarovski@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ lazarlazarovski (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Lead Generation Web Solutions Negotiation

Lazar Lazarovski - Facebook Ads Manager

Highly targeted impact marketing Facebook ads to generate interest, brand awareness and sales for a range of products and services | Facebook Ads Expert | Purely eCommerce focused Gevgelija

Summary

My focus is set on creating and optimising Facebook ads for variety of products in the eCommerce industry.

I've been working in the E-commerce (online shops) sector for more than 3 years including Dropshipping and affiliate marketing.

I was a part of a project that grew from 0-500k+ followers on SMM and brought minimum 50 sales per day.

When working with clients the most important part for me is the communication because it leads to understanding where the client stands, what are the challenges they face, create a research on how to help them in solving them, designing a strategy and implement it.

Experience

Stelar.mk

Facebook Ads Manager and Social Media Manager August 2019 - Present (2 years 1 month)

Gevgelija, Southeastern, North Macedonia

At Stelar.mk I am responsible for creating and optimising the Facebook Ads campaigns for different products.

My responsibilities include:

- → Adding and managing products
- Creating content for different variety of products
- ⇒ On-Page SEO through strategic keyword optimization in meta tags and content
- Creating a product catalog for Facebook Ads

- → Create a product feed for Facebook Ads
- → Creating and planning targeting strategy for different product niches
- → Monitoring and modifying Facebook ads based on analytics and sales
- ⇒ 1.3% CTR based on 3M impressions and 33K clicks in an industry that averages CTR is 0.51%

Nikmit

Facebook Ads Specialist September 2018 - July 2019 (11 months) Strumica, Southeastern, North Macedonia

At Nikmit I've started my career in digital marketing as a Facebook Ads Specialist and content writing executive.

I was in charge of creating compelling content for different variety of products with the goal to create ads that generate high conversion rate and sales.

Due to my stay at Nikmit my responsibilities included:

- → Managing paid ad campaigns across Facebook and Instagram
- ⇒ Building Facebook Advertising campaigns
- → Overseeing campaigns across a number of different product lines
- → Managing a monthly budget of +\$20K
- → Achieving result of minimum 100 sales per day in a limited market

Education

Univerzitet 'Sv. Kiril i Metódij' vo Skopje Bachelor's degree, GIS · (2012 - 2016)